特別
獻禮
音
樂
獎
視
電
大
人人影視
YYeTs.com
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
原創翻譯  中文字幕
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯: 某豚  萌Su
翻譯: 西西oishi  Mondo
翻譯: 木瓜一號  天緯
*I can feel my heart*
翻譯: 彭小小安   LOTTIE筱妤
翻譯: 草莓君  tungyip
翻譯: 甜土豆  薯薯秀
*Beating in your hands*
翻譯: 海倫  西蘭花小小姐
時間軸: aaaBao  言
*My aura and yours*
時間軸: Kallen  Ans
時間軸: 寶寶  貝貝
*Meeting in this dance*
校對: 澤川  豆丁
校對: 草莓花  噎死青春
*Pull the trigger*
校對: 笨熊貓 西之
*I'm ready, it's showtime*
后期&特效: 寶寶
總監: 澤川  噎死青春
*I stand here waiting for you to bang the gong*
*To crash the critic saying*
*Is it right or is it wrong*
*If only fame had an IV, baby could I bear*
*Being away from you, I found the vein, put it in here*
*I live for the applause, applause, applause*
*I live for the applause-plause*
*Live for the applause-plause*
*Live for the way that you cheer and scream for me*
*The applause, applause, applause*
*Give me that thing that I love (turn the lights on)*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch (make it real loud)*
*A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E*
*Make it real loud*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch*
*A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E*
*Make it real loud*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch*
*I've overheard your theory*
*Nostalgia's for geeks*
*I guess sir, if you say so*
*Some of us just like to read*
*One second I'm a kunst*
*Then suddenly the kunst is me*
*Pop culture was in art*
*Now, art's in pop culture in me*
*I live for the applause, applause, applause*
*I live for the applause-plause*
*Live for the applause-plause*
*Live for the way that you cheer and scream for me*
*The applause, applause, applause*
*Give me that thing that I love (turn the lights on)*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch (make it real loud)*
*A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E*
*Make it real loud*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch*
*A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E*
*Make it real loud*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch*
*Touch, touch*
*Touch, touch, now*
*I live for the applause, applause, applause*
*I live for the applause-plause*
*Live for the applause-plause*
*Live for the way that you cheer and scream for me*
*The applause, applause, applause*
一起來
*Give me that thing that I love (turn the lights on)*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch (make it real loud)*
*A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E*
*Make it real loud*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch*
*A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E*
*Make it real loud*
*Put your hands up, make'em touch, touch*
*A-R-T-P-O-P*
歡迎收看《2013年MTV音樂電視大獎》
正在布魯克林直播
今夜群星云集
女士們先生們  來自新片
《單向樂隊：這就是我們》
有請One Direction樂隊
布魯克林  你們好嗎
親們  很高興今晚能來到這里
來到頒獎禮現場  來到布魯克林
我們確實來自英國
但今晚的音樂電視大獎
讓全世界的歌手匯聚一堂
在紐約布魯克林一同歡慶
現在我們要看看紐約粉絲最棒的說法
到底是不是真的
我們去年贏得了三個獎項
TS: 閉上尼瑪的嘴
手握月球人獎杯的感覺無與倫比啊
我們很高興頒發今晚的第一個獎項
以下是"最佳流行錄影帶獎"的提名
流
錄
最
獎
佳
帶
行
影
獲得"最佳流行錄影帶獎"的是
Selena Gomez
快來拿吧[Come & Get it]
這獎杯夠沉  老天啊
這是我的第一座月球人獎杯
非常感謝大家
這一年對我來說意義非凡
這離不開你們的支持
謝謝你們  簡直太酷了  謝謝
我愛你們  保重
"潛力新人獎"得主由您決定
快來為心儀的提名歌手投票
支持Austin Mahone
請發送字母A至22444
Iggy Azalea
發送字母B
The Weeknd
發送字母C
Twenty One Pilots
發送字母D
Zedd
發送字母E
潛
人
力
獎
新
2013年"潛力新人獎"投選活動
由塔可鐘傾情贊助
請登錄MTV官方網站
或發送短信至22444進行投票
Katy Perry正在向布魯克林大橋進發
準備嗨翻全場的壓軸表演
接下來
Miley和Robin Thicke將共同登臺
稍后  Justin Timberlake將獻上
其歌唱生涯中最隆重的表演
或許他不是一個人哦
《2013年MTV音樂電視大獎》
由以下商家贊助
塔可鐘  生活添滋味
百事可樂  活在當下
程度配合運動覺技術
越動越保護
全新起亞秀爾
更安全  更精致
Beats by Dr.Dre  Beats膠囊音響
小身材大音量
百事可樂邀您來決定
Katy Perry的下支新單曲
在線試聽  推特投票
稍后一同欣賞Katy的精彩表演
類
獲
技
單
術
名
獎
錄 像 帶
藝
最
導
佳
指
"最佳錄像帶藝術指導"
術
錄 像 帶
最
舞
佳
編
"最佳錄影帶編舞"
錄 像 帶
攝
"最佳錄像帶攝影"
最
像
佳
錄
帶
最
演
"最佳錄影帶導演"
佳
導
影
錄
帶
最
佳
輯
像
剪
"最佳錄像帶剪輯"
錄 像 帶
視
最
果
佳
效
"最佳錄像帶視覺效果"
覺
后臺
女士們先生們
現在播放的是《好景當前》
稍后將播出《分歧者》片段
歡迎Shailene Woodley和Miley Cyrus
Miley  我喜歡你的新造型
真是酷斃了
能來VMA現場簡直酷爆了
因為我可以
我想吐舌頭就吐舌頭
還能跟泰迪熊跳舞神馬的
沒錯  必須酷斃了
哇哦  說到酷事
女士們先森們
有請...  先森們是啥
掌聲有請Robin Thicke和...
Miley Cyrus
來點掌聲
*It's our party, we can do what we want (no drama)*
*It's our party, we can do what we want*
*It's our party, we can say what we want*
*It's our party, we can love who we want*
*We can kiss who we want*
*We can screw who we want*
*Red cups and sweaty bodies everywhere*
*Hands in the air like we don't care*
*'Cause we came to have so much fun now*
*Bet somebody here might get some now*
*If you're not ready to go home*
*Can I get a "Hell no"*
*'Cause we gonna go all night*
*'Til we see the sunlight, alright*
*So la da di da di, we like to party*
*Dancing with Miley*
*Doing whatever we want*
*This is our house*
*This is our roof*
*And we can't stop*
*And we won't stop*
*Can't you see it's we who own the night*
*Can't you see it we who 'bout that life*
*And we can't stop*
*And we won't stop*
*We run things, things don't run we*
*Don't take nothing from nobody*
*It's our party, we can do what we want*
*It's our party, we can say what we want*
*It's our party, we can love who we want*
*We can kiss who we want*
*We can screw who we want*
*It's our party, we can do what we want to*
*It's our house, we can love who we want to*
*It's our song, we can sing if we want to*
*It's my mouth, I can say what I want to*
*And we can't stop*
*And we won't stop*
*We run things, things don't run we*
*Don't take nothing from nobody*
*Yeah, yeah, yeah*
*We can do what we want*
*We can do what we want to*
*Everybody get up*
*If you can't hear*
*What I'm tryin' to say*
*If you can't read from the same page*
*Maybe I'm going deaf (hey hey hey)*
*Maybe I'm going blind (hey hey hey)*
*Maybe I'm out of my mind (hey hey hey)*
*OK now he was close*
*Tried to domesticate ya*
*But you're an animal*
*Baby it's in your nature*
*Just let me liberate you (hey hey hey)*
*You don't need no takers (hey hey hey)*
*That man is not your maker (hey hey hey)*
*And that's why I'm gon' take a good girl*
*I know you want it*  *You know I want it baby*
*I know you want it*  *Oh yes I do*
*I know you want it*
*But you're a good girl, yes you are*
*Far from plastic*
*I'm talkin' about (blurred lines)*
*Yes I am*
*I know you want it*
*I know you want it baby*
*So come...come on*
*But you're a good girl, yes you are*
*I'm talkin' about*
*I'm talking*
*I'm talkin' talkin' about (blurred lines)*
*Okay baby*
*All I got to say baby*
*That's Robin baby*
*And I'm 2 Chainz baby*
*Highly respected (baby)*
*Black Michael Jackson*
*When the DJ bring it back*
*I pump it back like a chiropractor*
*I'm at the main event*
*Baby you the main attraction*  *Yes I am*
*What I need a script and a camera for*
*Let's put this thing in action (do it)*
*2 Chainz*
*All the things collapsing (do it)*
*Let's put this thing in action (do it)*
*Let's put this thing in action*
*2 Chainz*
*Gave your girl a chain reaction*
*You're like a needle in a haystack*
*I wanna sit you where my face at*
*Lunch with a few Mai-Tais*
*Purple kisses on my tie*
*Life can leave a dick loved*
*Now you gettin' this dick, love*
*I'm lookin' for you with a flashlight*
*I wanna feel what a real fat ass like*
*No injection, I learned my lesson*
*I walk it like I talk it, baby this pedestrian*
*Runnin' through your mind like Jackie Joyner*
*Pussy like pop, go give me a burner*
*Got shot like pop*
*This can be detrimental*
*T-shirt and panties, that's your credential*
*You're cotton candy, I need a fistful*
*I'm often antsy, hope that convince you*
*Hey girl*
*You know you're lookin' so damn fine*
*You're lookin' like you fell from the sky (angel)*
*You know you make a grown man cry*
*I wanna give it to you, through the night*
*And make everything you fantasize*
*Come true, ooh baby*
*I'll make you so, so, so amazing*
*I'll give it to you (tonight)*
*Oh yeah, baby*
*I gotta give it to you*
*I need you to move it*
*I need a Thicke's night*
*I gotta, I gotta... I gotta give it to you*
各位觀眾  有請Iggy Azalea和Lil Kim
我們先向布魯克林女王致敬
她激勵了我和眾多歌手
布魯克林的觀眾們
為女王Lil Kim歡呼吧
音樂電視大獎居然在布魯克林舉辦了
我的天吶
我愛死你們啦
我在布魯克林長大
從未想過VMA會來到我的家鄉
布魯克林小子們
了不起的布魯克林小子們
布魯克林崛起啦
嘻哈音樂已席卷全球
澳大利亞的Iggy也站在了我身邊
這充分證明嘻哈音樂走向了世界
請看"最佳嘻哈錄影帶獎"的提名
我愛你們
嘻
錄
最
獎
佳
帶
哈
影
我們一起打開
然后你宣布獲獎者
獲得"最佳嘻哈錄影帶獎"的是
Macklemore & Ryan Lewis
天吶
天吶  恭喜你們
給你  等下  這唇印我看不下去了
謝謝  太感謝啦
我喜歡這首歌
獨立嘻哈歌手也上音樂電視大獎啦
首先  向其他提名者致敬
我們居然拿到了一座月球人獎杯
這真是太瘋狂了
一切起源于一個想法
有這么一面旗幟
象征著我們的旅途
這面旗幟將走遍世界
我們有很多想法
我想乘海盜船  騎駱駝
跟雷鬼頭同伴去冰穴冒險
都融入進了這支音樂錄像帶
有很多...
謝謝
我們要感謝很多人
感謝經紀人Zach Quillen
Tricia Davis
我的女朋友Jackie
Jenny和Jason Conan
MV導演Jon Jon Augustavo
感謝Pierson 88
還有Josh和Peter
Ray Dalton
我肯定沒說全
感謝我的家人
感謝全世界的粉絲
是你們成就了我們的現在
謝謝我的未婚妻
你是我一生的摯愛
謝謝  Tricia Davis
我挺你到底  你懂得
Kevin Hart精彩吐槽之后
Kanye West將登臺獻唱
女士們先生們
有請新片《伴警執勤》
主演Kevin Hart
你們好嗎
你們得賣力點
紐約布魯克林
音樂電視大獎直播中
歡呼吧
縱情歡呼吧  大伙
大家都嗨起來吧
首先我要說清楚
我今年可不是主持
我只想上臺來  吐吐槽
抒發胸臆罷了
先說說開場表演吧
Lady Gaga太棒了
為她鼓掌吧  簡直是天才
親  Lady Gaga有美臀喲
我一直都不知道呢
她現在就露著屁屁  哥盯著呢
一直盯著呢拜托
Miley Cyrus  Robin Thicke
來歡呼一下
真棒  很不錯
Miley  這么"激戰"一番
你最好去驗驗孕吧
Robin穿著企鵝燕尾服就來了
明明是斑馬好嗎
好看  Robin
我喜歡  真的
VMA啊  大家歡呼起來
喊起來
再強調一次  我不是主持
我就在這里吐吐槽罷了
Taylor和Selena
我知道你們都來了
你們還年輕
離Robin遠點
好嗎  離他遠點
除非你不怕惹孕在身
一定要坐好了
Kendrick Lamar光臨盛會
我看到你了  Kendrick
Kendrick可能是現在嘻哈界最活躍的
他的歌詞里
他的歌詞里誰都提了
就是沒提過一個人
Chocolate Droppa  就是他
Kevin的"嘻哈自我"
你沒他的水準對吧  Kendrick
嘻哈真我  MTV也不待見
我在這里吐個槽
熱水熱狗任我拿
胡言亂語也不怕  小賤人
這就是真說唱
大伙  我要提醒你們
"潛力新人獎"的投票仍在進行
都快去投票吧
聽我的準沒錯
我是Kevin Hart
這里是音樂電視大獎
再次歡呼吧
投票給Austin Mahone
短信發送A至22444
投票給Iggy Azalea發送B
投票給The Weeknd發送C
投票給Twenty One Pilots發送D
投票給Zedd發送E
"潛力新人獎"由塔可鐘贊助
投票請登陸官網
或發送短信至22444
女士們先生們  有請Jared Leto
下一位歌手被譽為
世上最棒的搖滾之星
他是音樂界的邁克爾·喬丹
絕對的Jimmy Hendrix
被譽為最偉大的電吉他手
他無與倫比  他是搖滾之神
這些都是他形容他的
準備好了嗎  布魯克林
- 說"阿門"  - 阿門
- 哈利路亞  - 哈利路亞
- 萬能的上帝  - 萬能的上帝
掌聲歡迎Yeezy本尊Kanye West
Kanye別稱
*Strange fruit hanging from the poplar trees*
*I just need to clear my mind now*
*It's been racin' since the summertime (breathe)*
*And I'm holdin' down the summer now (breathe)*
*And all I want is what I can't buy now (I don't need)*
*'Cause I ain't got the money on me right now*
*And I told you to wait (breathe)*
*Yeah I told you to wait (breathe)*
*So I'mma need a little more time now (I don't need)*
*'Cause I ain't got the money on me right now*
*And I thought you could wait (breathe)*
*Yeah, I thought you could wait (breathe)*
*These bitches surroundin' me (thay body)*
*All want somethin' on me (breathe)*
*Then they talk about me (breathe)*
*Would be lost without me*
*We could've been somebody (strange fruit hanging)*
*Thought you'd be different 'bout it (from the poplar trees)*
*Now I know you not it (from the poplar trees)*
*So let's get on with it*
*You could've been somebody*
*'Stead you had to tell somebody*
*Let's take it back to the first party*
*When you tried your first ...*
*And came out of your body*
*Running naked down the lobby*
*And you was screamin' that you love me*
*Before the limelight tore ya*
*Before the limelight stole ya*
*Remember we were so young*
*When I would hold ya*
*Before the blood on the leaves*
*Leaves*
*I know there ain't wrong with me*
*Strange*
*Something strange is happening to me*
*You could've been somebody*
*We could've*
*we could've been somebody*
*Or was it on the first party*
*When we tried our first ...*
*And came out of our body*
*Before they call lawyers*
*Before you tried to destroy us*
*How you gon' lie to the lawyer*
*It's like I don't even know ya*
*I gotta bring it back to the 'nolia*
*Fuck them other niggas cause I'm down with my niggas*
*I ride with my niggas, I'll die for my*
*Die*
*Awesome*
下節"最佳女歌手錄影帶獎"
稍后Justin Timberlake將帶來
精彩的"先鋒獎"獲獎演出
《2013年MTV音樂電視大獎》
由以下贊助
奧比特口香糖
清新口氣神清氣爽  就嚼奧比特
簡單又透氣  封面女郎更佳選擇
Windows手機
關注410萬像素Windows手機
重新詮釋生活
諾基亞Lumia 1020
州立農業保險公司
州立農業保險公司  自助家庭銀行
為汽車  家庭  人壽  金融  提供更佳保障
*Lose yourself to dance*
*I know you don't get a chance to take a break this often*
*I know your life is speeding and it isn't stopping*
*You take my shirt and just go ahead and wipe up all the*
*Sweat, sweat, sweat*
*Lose yourself to dance*
*Come on, come on, come on, come on*
請掌聲歡迎Pharrell Williams
Nile Rodgers以及Daft Punk
我很榮幸
能和我的三位英雄共同頒獎
Nile Rodgers  曾與麥當娜
大衛·鮑威還有邁克爾·杰克遜合作過
還有這兩機器人老兄
嘿  Pharrell
但我們來這是為了另一群藝人
我們為"最佳女歌手錄影帶獎"提名而來
女
錄
最
獎
佳
帶
歌
手
影
"最佳女歌手錄影帶獎"
獲獎者是...
Taylor Swift
你們好
老天  謝謝
我是你們的忠實粉絲
我想感謝粉絲們
我經常發推說這事兒
我真的很想拿這個獎
非常謝謝你們的支持
我很幸運
因為影片導演Anthony Mandler
和聯合主演Reeve Carney今晚都在場
我很高興他們都在場
這感覺真是太棒了
我還想感謝給了我寫這歌靈感的人
那人是誰他自己心里清楚
讓我得到了這個獎
真是謝謝你啦
女士們先生們
有請獲得
"最佳男歌手錄影帶獎"候選人Ed Sheeran
大家好
音樂錄影帶不僅僅能用來娛樂
它們能改變我們看世界的方法
并激勵我們行動起來
接下來的錄影帶是其中佼佼者
下面是"最勵志錄像帶獎"提名
Beyoncé  《I Was Here》
Kelly Clarkson  《People Like Us》
Macklemore & Ryan Lewis和Mary Lambert
《Same Love》
Miguel  《Candles in the Sun》
Snoop Lion及Drake和Cori B.
《No Guns Allowed》
"最勵志錄像帶獎"的得主是
Macklemore & Ryan Lewis和Mary Lambert
《Same Love》
實話實說
我最想贏得"最佳說唱錄影帶獎"
但是此時此刻這個獎的意義更深遠
我從十五歲左右開始創作歌曲
在我所寫的所有歌曲中
這首歌對我而言最為重要
去年這首歌紅遍全球
見證了美國正發生的重大變化
同性戀權利就是人權
這兩者密不可分
我們創作了這首歌
但是不知道如何做好這支錄影帶
是Ryan Lewis  Tricia Davis
和Jon Jon Augustavo
讓這首歌煥發生機
制作《Same Love》的團隊
是制作《Can't Hold Us》和
《Thrift Shop》的原班人馬
這些歌曲的錄影帶都靠我們自己完成
有一些人的名字我必須提及
Noah Jolles和小號手Owuor Arunga
非常感謝  再次感謝我們的歌迷
這對我們來說意義重大
當然還要感謝Mary Lambert
您仍有時間來決定Katy Perry的先行單曲
在線收聽  并通過推特投票
不要錯過Katy今晚的表演
由百事可樂為您呈現
女士們先生們  掌聲歡迎Jimmy Fallon
在近11年前的2002年
我在無線電城音樂廳主持了當年的VMA
那夜將載入史冊
當然不是因我主持的緣故
而是因為那晚一位新晉的單飛歌手
首次登臺演出
他的名字是Justin Timberlake
正如人們所說  他創造了歷史
布魯克林  世界已經聚焦于此
讓我們來聽聽現場的歡呼
他將令你心醉神迷
他來了  流行樂總統
歡迎Justin Timberlake
*Ain't nobody love you like I love you*
*I wanna rock your body*
*And as long as I got my suit and tie*
*Cry me a river-er, yea, yea*
*My love, love*
*Gonna be back*
*Senorita, I feel for you*
*Bet I'll have you naked*
*By the end of this song*
*Yeah, this was your city*
*You did it all and more*
*Broke every law except for one, babe*
*Attraction, are you ready*
*I know you feel it*
*Pull you nearer 'til you feel it again, oh*
*(I wanna do something right) alright*
*But we can do something better*
*Ain’t no time like tonight*
*And we ain't trying to save it 'til later*
*Stay out here living the life*
*Nobody cares who we are tomorrow*
*You got that lil' something I like*
*A little something I've been wanting to borrow*
*Tonight the night's come on surrender*
*I won't lead your love astray, astray, yeah*
*Your love's a weapon*
*Give your body some direction*
*That's my aim*
*Then, we could (take back the night)*
*Come on*
*Use me up until there's nothing left*
*Take back the night*
*Dizzy, spinning, sweating*
*You can't catch your breath*
*Take back the night*
*Ooh, don't know when the sun is rising next*
*So if the feeling's right*
*Then raise your glass and let's*
*Take back the night*
*Alright*
*I'm bringin' sexy back*
*Them other boys don't know how to act*
*I think it's special what's behind your back*
*So turn around and I'll pick up the slack*
*Take it to the bridge*
*Dirty Babe*
*You see these shackles baby I'm your slave*
*I'll let you whip me, if I misbehave*
*It's just that no one makes me feel this way*
嗨起來
*Go head be gone with it*
*Come on let me see what you're working with*
*I still round this bitch*
*You make me smile*
*Go head be gone with it*
*Get your sexy on*
*Go head be gone with it (get your sexy on)*
*You ready (yes)*
*I kind of noticed from one eye*
*In the club, your frown face*
*It's kind of weird to me*
*Since you're so fine*
*If it's up to me your face will change*
*If you smile then that should set the tone*
*Just be limber*
*I will guide*
*If you let go
*The music should move your bones*
*Just remember*
*What*
*Sing this song with me*
*Can't nobody love you like I love you*
*You're a good girl*
*And that's what makes me trust ya*
*Late at night, I talk to you*
*You will know the difference*
*If I wrote you a love note*
*And made you smile with every word I wrote*
*What would you do*
*Would that make you want to change your scene*
*And wanna be the one on my team*
*Tell me, would you*
*What's the point of waiting anymore*
*'Cause girl I've never been more sure*
*That baby,it's you*
*This ring here represents my heart*
*Everything that you've been waiting for*
*Just say I do*
布魯克林  再來一遍
*I can see us holding hands*
*Walking on the beach, our toes in the sand*
*I can see us on the countryside*
*Sitting on the grass, laying side by side*
*You could be my baby, let me make you my lady*
*Girl, you amaze me*
*Ain't gotta do nothing crazy*
*See, all I want you to do is be my love*
*Love (My love)*
*Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love*
*Love*
*You don't have to say (what you did)*
*Come on*
*I already know, I found out from him*
*Now there's just no chance*
*No chance (for you and me)*
*There'll never be*
*And don't it make you sad about it*
*Cry me a river*
手舉起來
我現在要試試這個
布魯克林的男孩女孩們唱起來
*It feels like something's heating up*
*Can I leave with you*
*And then the ladies said*
*I don't know what I'm thinking bout*
*Really leaving with you*
大聲點
*It feels like something's heating up*
*Can I leave with you*
*Like that*
*I don't know what I'm thinking bout*
*Really leaving with you*
手舉起來
*It feels like something's heating up*
*Can I leave with you*
*I don't know what I'm thinking bout*
*Really leaving with you*
*It feels like something's heating up*
*Can I leave with you*
*I don't know what I'm thinking bout*
*Really leaving with you*
*Got time, but I don't mind*
*Just wanna rock you girl*
*I'll have whatever you have*
*Come on, just give it up girl*
*See I've been watching you*
*I like the way you move*
*So go ahead, girl, just do*
舉起手來
*That ass shakin' thing you do*
*So you grab your girls*
*And you grab a couple more*
*And you all can meet me*
*In the middle of the floor*
*Said the air is thick, it's smelling right*
*So you blast to the left*
*And you sail to the right*
*Don't be so quick to*
*Walk away (dance with me)*
*I wanna rock your body*
*Please stay (dance with me)*
*You don't have to admit you*
*Wanna play (dance with me)*
*Just let me rock you*
*Till the break of day*
*Now all the ladies give it to me*
*Talk to me boy*
*No disrespect*
*I don't mean no harm*
*Talk to me boy*
*I can't wait to have you in my arm*
*Time to take a chance*
*Hurry up*
*Come on babe*
*By the end of this song*
這是你們要求的
你們要求的合體
*Would you be my girlfriend*
哥們  開唱吧
*Ever since I saw your face*
*Nothing in my life has been the same*
*I walk around just saying your name*
*Without you my world would end*
*I've searched around this whole damn place*
*And everythings says you were meant to be*
*My girlfriend, oh*
*Bye bye*
*Bye bye bye*
*Don't wanna be a fool for you*
*Just another player in your game for two*
*You may hate me but it ain't no lie*
*Bye bye bye*
*Don't really wanna make it tough*
*I just wanna tell you that I've had enough*
*Might sound crazy but it ain't no lie*
*Bye bye bye*
*Baby baby baby*
N'Sync
*I be on my suit and tie shit, tie shit, tie*
今晚開心嗎
*I be on my suit and tie shit, tie shit*
你們玩的高興嗎
*Can I show you a few things*
*A few things, a few things, little baby*
*You ready*
*I can't wait 'til I get you on the floor, good-looking*
*Going out so hot, just like an oven*
*Owww, burned myself but just had to touch it*
*It's so fire and it's all mine*
*Hey baby, we don't mind all the watching*
*'Cause if they study close, real close they might learn something*
*She ain't nothing but a little doozy when she does it*
布魯克林  跟我唱
*And as long as I've got my suit and tie*
*I'm leave it off on the floor tonight*
*And you got fixed up too tonight*
*Let me show you a few things*
*All dressed up in black and white*
*And you're dressed in that dress I like*
*Love is swinging in the air tonight*
*Let me show you a few things*
唱起來
*Show you a few things*
大聲點
*About love*
*Let me show you a few things*
*Show you a few things*
*Aren't you somethin' to admire*
*'Cause your shine is somethin' like a mirror*
*And I can't help but notice, you reflect in this heart of mine*
*If you ever feel alone and the glare makes me hard to find*
*Just know that I'm always parellel on the other side*
唱給我聽
*'Cause with your hand in my hand and a pocket full of soul*
*I can tell you there's no place we couldn't go*
*Just put your hand on the past*
*I'm here tryin' to pull you through*
*You just gotta be strong*
*'Cause I don't wanna lose you now*
*I'm lookin' right at the other half of me*
*The vacancy that set in my heart*
*Is a space, now you hold*
你們唱的太棒了
*Show me how to fight for now*
*And I'll tell you baby, it was easy*
*Comin' back into you once I figured it out*
*You were right here all along*
一起來  再來一遍
*It's like you're my mirror*
*My mirror staring back at me*
*I couldn't get any bigger*
*With anyone else beside of me *
*And now it's clear as this promise*
*That we're making two reflections into one*
*'Cause it's like you're my mirror*
*My mirror staring back at me, staring back at me *
停
該你們  唱出來
謝謝
謝謝你們
非常感謝
掌聲送給Justin Timberlake
這讓我...
怡芳出手  所向披靡  哥要咋辦啊
跪拜Justin Timberlake啊各位
謝肥倫
我不知道...
你們能感受到現場的激情嗎
現場各位都萬分激動
太不可思議了
我們愛你  兄弟
我可以用長篇大論闡述Justin何德何能受此殊榮
但我覺得原因很明顯  對吧
我很榮幸能夠站在你旁邊
給你頒發"邁克爾·杰克遜先鋒錄影帶獎”
Justin今晚獲獎是理所當然
因為在過去二十年里
他一直在娛樂大眾
他成為了傳奇
從N'Sync開始
多傳奇的組合
真的做到了啊
再到他的個人專輯
他一波一波又一波的熱門單曲
我說的是《Sexy Back》
《Cry Me A River》
順便說一句  那首歌寫的是我
還有《Dick in a Box》
JT和SNL惡搞組合Lonely Island合作的歌曲
《Dick in a Box》啊
我說的是14個MTV音樂電視大獎
還有《The 20/20 Experience》
登頂全球的音樂榜單
關于這家伙  還有什么好說的
他是這個行業里的翹楚
女士們先生們
掌聲獻給我的朋友  傳奇人物
Justin Timberlake先生
真為你驕傲  你做到了
Justin  Justin  Justin  Justin
好吧  這真是...
沒錯
你們每人的禮包里都多了500美元
就為你們這歡呼聲
我要帶Jimmy去巡演  他太能說了
那是我必須說的  我不敢相信
我現在還是下去吧
來嘛  別走  把基情進行到底
我不配這個獎
可我不打算把獎還回去
我要把它帶回家
每一個我有幸合作過的音樂錄影帶導演
這個獎得歸功于你們
我的經紀人  Johnny  我的父母
但最重要的是
我獲得的一半月球人獎杯
都是和那四位同伴一起獲得的
所以  最重要的是
我要與...  獎杯得放在我家
但我要與他們分享這個獎
這是莫大的榮譽  謝謝大家
謝謝大家
接下來
Macklemore & Ryan Lewis聯手驚喜嘉賓
進行VMA首演
之后  Katy Perry首次帶來
她職業生涯中的最熱門單曲
另外  即將揭曉的獎項是
由Windows手機贊助的"夏日最佳歌曲"
2013年MTV音樂電視大獎
韋里孫  你強大的通訊公司
特洛伊"心醉神迷"安全套
特洛伊  全美銷量第一安全套
以及簡單清新美麗  封面女郎化妝品贊助播出
2013年MTV音樂電視大獎正在火熱進行中
在我們的DJ棚里
我們看到許多紅毯的驚艷"封面時刻"
我尤其喜歡Emeli Sandé的煙熏妝
最新的封面女郎Becky G
看起來美極了  那光澤滿滿的雙唇
當然還有Rita Ora代表英國而來
- 她化什么妝都好看  - 的確
根據我們的觀察
很明顯  夸張的眼妝和大膽的唇妝
是今年的流行趨勢
想要分享你的封面時刻
請登錄covermoment.com
你將有機會參加明年的VMA頒獎禮
這里是布魯克林巴克萊中心
舉辦的2013年MTV音樂電視大獎現場
由Windows手機贊助的
"夏日最佳歌曲"獎項即將頒出
整周使用全方位觀看模式
諾基亞Lumia 1020重新定義了
粉絲們觀看VMA頒獎禮的方式
這里有名流采訪  嘻哈即興饒舌
甚至有性感的貼身舞蹈
這個獎項由Windows手機贊助設立
由你決定獎項歸屬
讓我們去看看誰獲獎了
首先  掌聲送給DJ Cassidy的表現
向他致以無盡的愛意
布魯克林  你們好嗎
我是DJ Cassidy  走起
*Calling all hearts*
*To the dance floor tonight*
我們開始吧
我要簡單提一下  各位
大家要清楚  我不是在主持
他們老是要我干這干那
但現在我上臺了
我想說說我剛才看的表演
首先  Justin Timberlake秒殺全場
掌聲送給Justin Timberlake
朋友們  他表演了將近20分鐘
實在太精彩了
他還把N'Sync帶回來了  我的天
我知道N'Sync生氣了
因為怡芳只讓他們表演了一首歌
他們絕對是生氣了
他們身材也走形了
他們發福了  對吧
他們跳舞的時候可累了
我看到Joey放屁了
愛放屁的Joey
你好  屁精
天吶
不過說真的  他的表演很精彩
Justin  我向你致敬
在宣布正事前我想說最后一句話
Lady Gaga還在現場嗎
她的翹臀太火辣了
天吶  Lady Gaga  我的媽呀
回座位時我要走過你的身旁
故意扔個東西在地上
只為把我的臉靠近你的翹臀
我會這么做的
下面我們進入正題吧
為Kanye鼓掌歡呼吧
為他的瘋狂表演歡呼
他剛才就像個神
你雖然看得到他
卻不確定他是否在那兒
像個影子  若隱若現
我很喜歡  很棒
別忘了  現在仍可以為"潛力新人獎"投票
大家去投票吧  快去
我是Kevin Hart
這次MTV電視音樂大獎碉堡了
大家嗨起來  待會兒見
發送A到22444為Austin Mahone投票
發送B為Iggy Azalea投票
發送C為The Weekend投票
發送D為Twenty One Pilots投票
發送E為Zedd投票
2013年的"潛力新人獎"投票
由塔可鐘傾情贊助
請登錄MTV官方網站
或發送短信至22444參與投票
掌聲有請Vampire Weekend
今年夏天  不管你身在何處
總有一些歌曲隨處都可以聽到
它們會出現在每位DJ的歌單上
在每個沙灘派對和燒烤聚會上播放
但只有一首歌能當選"夏日最佳歌曲"
幾周以來  你們都在為最愛那首投票
投票通道剛剛關閉
"夏日最佳歌曲"的提名曲目有
日
最
夏
曲
歌
佳
由你們票選出來的"夏日最佳歌曲"是...
*And we dance all night*
*To the best song ever*
- One Direction  - 1D哦
我想說  非常感謝你們
感謝我們的粉絲
能獲得這個獎都是你們的功勞
感謝所有為我們投票的人
這對我們來說意義重大
這位是錄影帶的導演
都是他的主意  Bes Winston
謝謝
Harry說啥我說啥
過去三年粉絲為我們做的
實在難以置信  非常感謝
我們的電影下周末就會推出了
這座月球人對我們意義重大
最后再對你們說一聲
謝謝大家
謝謝
掌聲歡迎Jason Collins和ASAP Rocky
在我出柜之前
我的奶奶對我說  她很擔心
我會像她在南方家鄉時那樣
遭受歧視和偏見
我知道
性取向歧視和種族歧視本質相同
只有一個辦法能改變別人的看法
就是勇敢地捍衛你的信仰
朋友們  我的專輯《Trap Lord》已經發售了
下一位表演嘉賓是我的好朋友
他勇敢地捍衛著他的一切信仰
無論是人人平等  種族還是同性戀
請把尖叫聲獻給我的兄弟
白人典范  Macklemore和Ryan Lewis
大家嗨起來
*When I was in the 3rd grade*
*I thought that I was gay*
*'Cause I could draw, my uncle was*
*And I kept my room straight*
*I told my mom*
*Tears rushing down my face*
*She's like, Ben you've loved girls*
*Since before pre-K*
*Tripping yeah*
*I guess she had a point, didn't she*
*A bunch of stereotypes all in my head*
*I remember doing the math like*
*Yeah I'm good at little league*
*A pre-conceived idea of what it all meant*
*For those that like the same sex*
*Had the characteristics*
*The right-wing conservatives think*
*It's a decision*
*And you can be cured with*
*Some treatment and religion*
*Man-made, rewiring of a pre-disposition*
*Playing God*
*Ahh nah, here we go*
*America the brave*
*Still fears what we don't know*
*And God loves all his children*
*It's somehow forgotten*
*But we paraphrase a book written*
*3,500 years ago*
*I don't know*
*And I can't change*
*Even if I tried*
*Even if I wanted to*
*And I can't change*
*Even if I tried*
*Even if I wanted to*
*My love my love my love*
*She keeps me warm*
*If I was gay*
*I would think hip-hop hates me*
*Have you read the YouTube comments lately*
*Man that's gay*
*Gets dropped on the daily*
*We've become so numb to what we're saying*
*Our culture founded from oppression*
*Yet we don't have acceptance for 'em*
*Call each other faggots*
*Behind the keys of a message board*
*A word rooted in hate*
*Yet our genre still ignores it*
*Gay is synonymous with the lesser*
*It's the same hate that's caused wars from religion*
*Gender to skin color*
*Complexion of your pigment*
*The same fight that lead people*
*To walk-outs and sit-ins*
*Human rights for everybody*
*There is no difference*
*Live on! And be yourself*
*When I was in church*
*They taught me something else*
*If you preach hate at the service*
*Those words aren't anointed*
*And that Holy Water*
*That you soak in*
*Is then poisoned*
*When everyone else*
*Is more comfortable*
*Remaining voiceless*
*Rather than fighting for humans*
*That have had their rights stolen*
*I might not be the same*
*But that's not important*
*No freedom till we're equal*
*Damn right I support it*
*I don't know*
*And I can't change*
*Even if I tried*
*Even if I wanted to*
*My love, my love, my love*
*She keeps me warm*
*We press play*
*Don't press pause*
*Progress, march on*
*With a veil over our eyes*
*We turn our back on the cause*
*'Till the day that my uncles can be united by law*
*Kids are walkin' around the hallway*
*Plagued by pain in their heart*
*A world so hateful*
*Some would rather die*
*Than be who they are*
*And a certificate on paper*
*Isn't gonna solve it all*
*But it's a damn good place to start*
*No law's gonna change us*
*We have to change us*
*Whatever god you believe in*
*We come from the same one*
*Strip away the fear*
*Underneath it's all the same love*
*About time that we raised up*
*And I can't change*
*Even if I tried*
*Even if I wanted to*
*My love, my love, my love*
*She keeps me warm*
一起來
*Love is patient*
*Love is kind*
*I'm not crying on Sundays (love is patient)*
*I'm not crying on Sundays (love is kind)*
*I'm not crying on Sundays*
說到改變
- 咱和他們不是一路吧  - 也許吧
但只有一試才知道
金發妞  快滾開
感覺你好像變了
但是我喜歡
你的駕照過期了嗎
你正帶著我駛向狂熱呢
- 把握機會喲  妹子  - 當然
有請Emeli Sandé和Adam Lambert
晚上好  布魯克林
見過眾多大牌后  也該照顧一下新人了
大家整晚都在為"潛力新人獎"投票
決定權在你們手中
獲提名的有
Austin Mahone
Iggy Azalea
The Weeknd
Twenty One Pilots
還有Zedd
本年度"潛力新人獎"已由你們選出
獲獎者是
Austin Mahone
- 多謝  - 不客氣
我的神吶
我都不知道該說什么了
這真的太棒了
首先要感謝MTV
感謝上帝讓我能來到這里
然后要謝謝老媽
她一直支持著我
單親媽媽養育我很不易
有她我就很知足了
老媽我愛你
接著要感謝我的好友
從最開始就支持我
我相信他們今后也一樣
AC  Robert  Zach  我愛你們
此外  要感謝我的團隊
Rocco  Mike  Ryan和Dave
感謝你們給予我機會  謝謝
感謝我的宣傳代理人Erica
她很出色
最后  我要深深感謝
我最親愛的粉絲們
謝謝你們  謝謝你們投票給我
我能站在這里  都是你們的功勞
非常感謝
這太不可思議了
非常感謝  大家晚安
女士們先生們
歡迎TLC組合的T-Boz和Chilli
- 姐們  - 姐們好
我和你說  下一位藝人...
我在后臺用耳機3D環繞聽歌
聽著Avila Brothers的歌嗨到不行
讓我告訴你
如果這位歌手邀你參加他加拿大的演唱會
你知道要怎么辦
- 我們得去啊  - 必須出現
必須去啊
他剛出道幾年
但已經是巨星水平
掌聲歡迎獨一無二的
- 帥氣的Drake  - Drake
*I got my eyes on you*
*You're everything that I see*
*I want your hot love and emotion*
*And lastly, I can't get over you*
*You left your mark on me*
*I want your hot love and emotion endlessly*
*'Cause you're a good girl and you know it*
*You act so different around me*
*Cause you're a good girl and you know it*
*I know exactly who you could be*
*Just hold on we're going home*
*It's hard to do these things alone*
*Started...*
準備好了嗎
*Started from the bottom now we're here*
*Started from the bottom now my whole team here*
*Started from the bottom now the whole team here*
一起來
*Started from the bottom now we're here*
*Started from the bottom now my whole team here*
我看見你們了
*Started from the bottom now the whole team here*
*I done kept it real from the jump*
*Living at my mama's house we'd argue every month*
*I was, I was trying to get it on my own*
*Working all night, traffic on the way home*
*And my uncle calling me like "Where ya at"*
*I gave you the keys told ya bring it right back*
*I just, I just think its funny how it goes*
*Now I'm on the road, half a million for a show*
*Started from the bottom now we're here*
*Started from the bottom now my whole team here*
*Started from the bottom now the whole team here*
*Started from the bottom now we're here*
*Started from the bottom now my whole team here*
*Started from the bottom now the whole team here*
*Boys tell stories about the man*
*Say I never struggled, wasn't hungry, yeah, I doubt it*
*I could, I could turn your boy into the man*
*There ain't really much I hear that's poppin' off without us*
*We just want the credit where it's due*
*I'ma worry about me*
*Just as a reminder to myself*
*I wear every single chain, even when I'm in the house*
*Started from the bottom now we're here*
*Started from the bottom now my whole team here*
我看見你們了
*Started from the bottom now the whole team here*
*No new no new, we don't feel that*
*Fuck a fake friend, where you real friends at*
*We don't like to do too much explaining*
*Story stays the same I never changed it*
再來一次
*No new*
*we don't feel that*
*Fuck a fake friend, where you real friends at*
*We don't like to do too much explaining*
*See, my story stay the same through the money and the fame*
*‘Cause we started from the bottom now we're here*
接下來  Taylor Swift將上臺頒發
"最佳男歌手錄影帶獎”
之后  布魯克林將迎來Bruno Mars
《2013年MTV音樂電視大獎》的贊助商有
Windows手機
關注410萬像素的Windows Phone
諾基亞Lumia 1020
Degree  用心關懷
越多運動  越多保護
塔可鐘
越活越精彩
奧比特口香糖
清新口氣讓你神清氣爽
有請Taylor Swift
很多事都難以抉擇
音樂電視大獎該穿什么鞋子
要和誰坐一起
以及五位才華橫溢的男歌手中
誰將摘得"最佳男歌手錄影帶獎"
只有一位將勝出
"最佳男歌手錄影帶獎"的提名如下
男
錄
最
獎
佳
帶
歌
手
影
"最佳男歌手錄影帶獎”的得主是
Bruno Mars  《Locked Out of Heaven》
非常感謝
這是我獲得的第一座月球人
我想感謝我的樂隊
感謝Cameron Duddy
和我合作拍攝了這支錄影帶
我的經紀人Brandon Creed
大西洋唱片的所有人
所有投票的粉絲們
我愛你們  謝謝你們
謝謝MTV  謝謝
Taylor Swift與眾多男歌手
一同角逐今夜最大獎項
"年度音樂錄影帶獎"
接著  將由Katy Perry獻上盛大壓軸表演
女士們先生們
今夏冠軍單曲和冠軍專輯得主
Selena Gomez
接下來的這位歌手
每每登臺都博得滿堂喝彩
女士們先生們  做好準備
他將帶來新單《Gorilla》
掌聲歡迎Bruno Mars
*Oh I got a bottle full of liquor with a cocaine kicker*
*And I'm feeling like I'm thirty feet tall*
*So lay it down, lay it down*
*You got your laser up in the sky*
*With the devil in your eyes*
*Let me hear you say you want it all*
*Say it now, say it now*
*Look what you just doing*
*Look what you done*
*But in this jungle you can't run*
*'Cause what I got for you*
*I promise is a killer, you'll be banging on my chest*
*Bang bang, gorilla*
*You and me baby making love like gorillas*
*Yeah I got a fistful on your head*
*But you don't look like you're scared*
*You're just smiling tell me daddy it's yours*
*'Cause you know how I like it use a dirty little lover*
*If the neighbors call the cops*
*Call the sheriff, call the SWAT we don't stop*
*We keep rocking while they knocking on our door*
*And you're screaming give it to me baby*
*Give it to me mother...*
*Oh look what you just doing*
*Look what you done*
*But in this jungle you can't run*
*'Cause what I got for you*
*I promise is a killer, you'll be banging on my chest*
*Bang bang, gorilla*
*You and me baby making love like gorillas*
*I bet you never ever felt so good, so good*
*I got your body trembling like it should, it should*
*You'll never be the same baby once I'm done with you*
*Oh you with me baby making love like gorillas*
*Baby*
*You and me baby making love like gorillas*
*Girl let me take my time*
*Take my time, take my time dear*
*I just want one smile*
*Want one smile, want one smile baby*
*Once I lay beside you, girl*
*I wanna make you scream, yeah, yeah*
*Let me take my time*
*Take my time, take my time dear*
*I just want one smile*
*Want one smile, want one smile baby*
*Once I ... you, girl*
*I wanna make you scream*
*Yeah, yeah, yeah*
*Oh, baby*
*C'mon, C'mon, C'mon, C'mon, C'mon, C'mon, baby*
*C'mon, C'mon, C'mon, baby*
*Baby*
接下來  Katy Perry在布魯克林的場外表演  百事為您呈現
稍后  是我們翹首企盼的獎項
"年度音樂錄影帶獎"
Katy Perry將首次演唱《Roar》
她史無前例的重磅新單
《2013MTV音樂電視大獎》
由以下商家贊助
州立農場
為您的汽車  家庭  生命  財產
提供更好的保險
Trojan激爽安全套
全美最受信賴的安全套品牌
全新起亞秀爾系列汽車
更加靈動  久經考驗
百事
活在當下
如需下載今晚的任何演唱
請登陸iTunes.com/VMAs
我現在位于美麗的布魯克林大橋公園
這里有百事可樂和許多Katy Perry的鐵桿粉絲
我們都無比興奮
因為Katy即將登臺
表演她的最新單曲《Roar》
今晚大家可以投票決定
《Prism》中的哪首歌成為下首新單
現在結果已經出來了
《Dark Horse》將于九月十七日發行
登錄Pepsi.MTV.com觀看Katy的獨家視頻
免費下載Katy的單曲《Roar》
機會有限  盡在百事
讓我聽到你們的咆哮[歌名]吧
女士們先生們
歡迎電影《唐璜》主演
Joseph Gordon-Levitt
謝謝  非常感謝  女士們先生們
令人期待的時刻到了
今晚最大的獎項
"年度音樂錄影帶獎"即將頒發
絕對的大獎哦
好的  以下是被提名的錄影帶
Macklemore & Ryan Lewis搭檔Wanz
《Thrift Shop》
Justin Timberlake  《Mirrors》
Bruno Mars  《Locked Out of Heaven》
Robin Thicke搭檔T.I.和Pharrell
《Blurred Lines》
Taylor Swift  《I Knew You Were Trouble》
獲得"年度音樂錄影帶獎"的是
我也不想用這種聲音說話
但是這地兒太大了
Justin Timberlake  《Mirrors》
你的介紹太贊了
請大家為Kanye  Bruno
以及所有人精彩的表演喝彩吧
你們今晚開心嗎
這支錄影帶對我來說很特別
它是獻給我的祖父母的
你這話就不對了
人人都有祖父母的啊
我繼續說  你們知道
我的爺爺去年十二月逝世了
我希望我的奶奶正在看電視
這是給你的  奶奶
Floria  我希望你在附近
我想了這么個點子
而你導演得簡直碉堡了
Jewels  Colin
以及每個幫助我制作錄影帶的人
這真的...  很不可思議
對我個人來說很重要
非常感謝
我愛你們  謝謝
歡迎《衰姐們》的主演Allison Williams
最后一位表演者
正緩緩走向布魯克林大橋
激動人心的時刻就要到了
她將首次表演她迄今最熱的單曲
女士們先生們
掌聲歡迎Katy Perry
*I used to bite my tongue and hold my breath*
*Scared to rock the boat and make a mess*
*So I sat quietly, agreed politely*
*I guess that I forgot I had a choice*
*I let you push me past the breaking point*
*I stood for nothing*
*So I fell for everything*
*You held me down, but I got up*
*Already brushing off the dust*
*You hear my voice, your hear that sound*
*Like thunder, gonna shake your ground*
*You held me down, but I got up*
*Get ready 'cause I've had enough*
*I see it all, I see it now*
*I got the eye of the tiger, the fire*
*Dancing through the fire*
*'Cause I am a champion*
*And you're gonna hear me roar*
*Louder, louder than a lion*
*'Cause I am a champion*
*And you're gonna hear me roar*
*You're gonna hear me roar*
*Now I'm floating like a butterfly*
*Stinging like a bee I earned my stripes*
*I went from zero, to my own hero*
*You held me down, but I got up*
*Already brushing off the dust*
*You hear my voice, your hear that sound*
*Like thunder, gonna shake your ground*
*You held me down, but I got up*
*Get ready 'cause I've had enough*
準備好了嗎  布魯克林
*I see it all, I see it now*
*I got the eye of the tiger, the fire*
*Dancing through the fire*
*'Cause I am a champion*
*And you're gonna hear me roar*
*Louder, louder than a lion*
翻譯: 某豚  萌Su
翻譯: 西西oishi  Mondo
*'Cause I am a champion*
*And you're gonna hear me roar*
翻譯: 木瓜一號  天緯
翻譯: 彭小小安   LOTTIE筱妤
翻譯: 草莓君  tungyip
翻譯: 甜土豆  薯薯秀
*You're gonna hear me roar*
翻譯: 海倫  西蘭花小小姐
時間軸: aaaBao  言
時間軸: Kallen  Ans
時間軸: 寶寶  貝貝
*You're gonna hear me roar*
校對: 澤川  豆丁
校對: 草莓花  噎死青春
校對: 笨熊貓  西之
后期&特效: 寶寶
總監: 澤川  噎死青春
*Roar, roar, roar, roar*
*Roar*
*I got the eye of the tiger, the fire*
*Dancing through the fire
*'Cause I am a champion*
*And you're gonna hear me roar*
*Louder, louder than a lion*
*'Cause I am a champion*
*And you're gonna hear me roar*
*You're gonna hear me roar*
比賽
結束
謝謝  布魯克林
晚安